I can't believe
you'd actually say that.
어떻게 그런 말을 하냐?
I'd much rather be Mr. Peanut
than Mr. Salty.
'짠돌이'보다는
'땅콩'이 훨씬 낫다구
무슨 소리, 그래도 '짠돌이'는
뱃사람이야
No way.
Mr. Salty is a sailor.
누구보다 터프한 사나이!
He's gotta be
the toughest snack there is.
난 잘 모르겠지만
옥수수는 못 만지게 해라
I don't know. You don't
wanna mess with Cornnuts.
They're crazy.
미쳐 돌아가신다
이럴 수가!
Oh, my God. You gotta come see this.
이럴 수가
얘들아, 저것 좀 봐
There's some creep out there
with a telescope.
어떤 변태가 망원경을 들고 있어
세상에, 우릴 보고 있잖아
I can't believe it.
He's looking right at us.
너무 역겹다
Oh, that is so sick.
I feel violated.
기분이 이상해
느낌이 아주 안 좋아
And not in a good way.
어떻게 저런 짓을 하지?
How can people do that?
세상에
얘들아, 저기 봐
못난이 벌거숭이가 부츠 신었어
You guys, look.
Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
The One With the Evil Orthodontist
앞으로 몇 년 후엔 학생들이
우릴 본보기 삼아 공부할걸
Years from now,
school children will study it...
...as one of the greatest
first dates ever.
역사적으로 기록될만한
첫 번째 데이트였다구
야호!
-Yeah.
-I'll say, yeah.
그건 내가 할 소리야
It was unbelievable.
우린 서로에게 빠져들었어
농담할 시간도 없었다니까
We could be ourselves.
We didn't have to play games.
그래서, 전화했어?
-Have you called her?
-She'd know I like her. That's crazy.
그럼 내가 좋아하는 거 알게?
미쳤어?
- 무슨 소리야?
- 정말 이해가 안 가
Guys. It's gross.
하루밖에 안 지났는데
얼마나 궁해 보이겠어?
It's the next day.
How needy do I wanna seem?
내 말이 틀려?
-I'm right. Right?
-Yeah, let her dangle.
- 그럼, 애를 태워야지
- 맞아
I can't believe my parents are
pushing me to find one of you people.
엄마 아빠가 왜 요런 인간들을
만나라고 볶으시는지 모르겠다
그러지 말고 그냥 해버려
Come on. Just do it.
전화를 걸어
남성 호르몬이 아깝지도 않니?
Call her.
Stop being so testosterone-y.
이런 게 바로
진정한 샌프란시스코 식이지
Which, by the way,
is the real San Francisco treat.
기계야
-Her machine.
-Answering machine?
응답기?
아니, 전화받는 기계가 받았어
No, interestingly,
her leaf blower picked up.
- 왜 아무 말 안 했어?
- 아니, 절대 안돼
So, why didn't you say anything?
No. Last time I left
a spontaneous message...
지난번에 '꼭, 꼬옥'이라고
메시지를 남겼단 말야
... I ended up using the phrase,
"Yes, indeed-io."
레이첼하고 배리야
안돼, 보지 마
Look, it's Rachel and Barry.
Don't everybody look.
둘이 뭐하고 있어?
What's going on?
그냥 얘기해
-They're just talking.
-Does he look upset?
화난 얼굴이야?
험하게 쏘아붙이는 분위기야?
Does he look like he was told
to shove anything?
아니, 웃고 있는데
그리고...
No. Actually, he's smiling.
- 안돼, 그러지 마
- 왜, 왜?
Oh, my God. Don't do that.
What? What? What?
길 건너에 서있는 남자가
비둘기를 발로 찼어
That man across the street
just kicked that pigeon.
그렇게 해서 법안이 법률로
만들어지는 거야
And basically, that's how
a bill becomes a law.
그렇구나
See? Hey, Rach.
- 안녕, 레이첼
- 안녕
어떻게 됐어?
How'd it go?
솔직히... 정말 좋았어
You know, it was actually
really great.
근사한 식당에서 점심을 먹었어
Lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
치킨을 먹었는데, 쿡 찌르니까
버터가 튀어나오더라
I had that chicken, where you poke it
and butter squirts out.
닭이 불쌍하다
Not a good day for birds.
그리고 시내에 갔는데,
싫다는데 샤넬 향수를 사주는 거야
Then we went to Bendel's.
And I told him not to, but he got me
a bottle of Chanel.
좋았겠네
That's nice. Now was that before
or after you told him...
근데 귀찮게 하지 말라고
말하기 전이야 말하고 나서야?
...to stop calling, stop sending
flowers and to leave you alone?
그런 얘기 꺼내지도 못했어
Right. Well, we never actually
got to that.
다시 보니까 정말 좋더라
It was just so nice to see him again.
편하고 익숙한 느낌이었어
정말 좋았어
It was comfortable
and it was familiar.
It was just nice.
정말 좋았단 말을
두 번이나 했어
That's nice twice.
어떻게 된 거야? 네가 결혼식장에
버리고 온 배리 아냐?
Isn't this the same Barry
who you left at the altar?
너 여태 어디 있었어?
Where have you been?
그렇긴 한데, 오늘은 달라 보였어
그냥 치열교정사가 아니었다구
It was different
with him today.
He wasn't, like, Orthodontist Guy.
I mean, we had fun.
Is there anything wrong with that?
정말 재미있었어
그럼 안 되는 거야?
안되지
-Why?
-I have my reasons.
- 왜?
- 말못할 사정이 있어
너랑 제일 친했던 친구랑
약혼했다는 사실을 잊은 거야?
He's engaged to another woman...
...who happens to be
your ex-best friend?
그래, 알았어
맞아, 어리석은 짓이야
All right.
I know it's stupid.
당장 찾아가서 끝내자고
말할 거야
I'll see him this afternoon
and put an end to it.
와우...
와우
그래
내가 미쳤나봐
전엔 이러지 않았잖아
I'm not crazy, right?
I mean, it was never like that.
이러지 않았지
No, it wasn't.
여기 귀여운 싱크대도 있네
It was so nice
having this little sink here.
Then with authority, hang up.
당국에서... 협의 중이야
그냥 메시지 남기면 되잖아
Will you just leave her the message?
알았어, 하면 되잖아
Okay. All right, fine.
다니엘,
응답기가 받을 줄은 몰랐네
"Oh, Danielle,
I wasn't expecting the machine.
시간 되면 전화 좀 해줘
Give me a call
when you get a chance.
안녕
Bye-bye.
살았다
Oh, God.
두 시간 동안 연습했던 게
고작 그거였어?
That's what you've been working on
for two hours?
얼마나 연습한 건데
Hey, I've been honing.
접시 소리는 뭐야?
-What was with the dishes?
-She might think I'm in a restaurant.
레스토랑에 있는 것처럼
하려고 그랬지
알잖아...
I might have a life.
Like I haven't been sitting here...
나도 생활이 있단 걸 보여줘야지
두 시간 동안 연습한 거 안 들키게
... honing for the last two hours?
저기 봐, 또 그런다
또 망원경으로 보고 있어
-The telescope guy's doing it again.
-Oh, my God.
기막혀
저리 가요
여기 그만 쳐다봐요
Go away.
Stop looking in here.
이젠 손까지 흔드네
Great.
Now he's waving back.
어떻게 해야지 안되겠어
We gotta do something.
아침엔 내 방을 쳐다보고
있더라구
I caught him looking into our place.
I feel like I can't do stuff.
정말 소름끼쳐
맘놓고 아무 것도 못하겠어
뭘 못 하는데?
What kind of stuff?
이상한 생각하나 본데
그런 거 아냐
Will you grow up?
I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
옷 벗고 요리하는 거 말야
...but, like,
when I'm cooking naked.
옷 벗고 요리해?
You cook naked?
그래, 토스트, 오트밀...
안 튀기는 거 있잖아
Yeah, toast, oatmeal.
Nothing that spatters.
왜 날 쳐다봐?
나도 몰랐단 말야
What are you looking at me for?
I didn't know that.
왜 그래?
What's the matter?
난...
배리, 이건 아냐
I just
Oh, Barry, this was not good.
아니긴
No, it was.
It was very, very good.
정말 정말 좋았어
민디는 어떻게 해?
-What about Mindy?
-Way better than Mindy.
민디보다 훨씬 좋았어
그런 얘기가 아냐
자기랑 민디, 어떡하냐구
I mean, what about you and Mindy?
If you want, I'll
break it off with her.
자기가 원하면
민디랑은 끝낼 거야
안돼, 안돼, 그러지 마
날 위해서라면 그러지 마
No, don't do that.
Not for me.
파베르 박사님
바비 러쉬가 왔습니다
Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush
is here for his adjustment.
고마워요
Thanks, Bernice.
주말에 여행 가자
Let's go away this weekend.
배리, 안돼
그럴 순 없어
-This is all way too
-No, we can go to Aruba.
아니, 우리 아루바에 가자
자기랑 신혼여행 가려고 했던
거길 가니까
When I went there on what
would've been our honeymoon...
정말 좋더라
자기도 좋아했을 거야
...it was really nice.
You would've liked it.
브래지어 어딨더라...
I had a bra.
파베르 박사님
Hey, Dr. Farber.
좋아요, 그린 양
이상없군요
All right, Miss Greene,
everything looks fine.
앞으로 진행상황을 더
지켜봐야 할 것 같습니다
We're starting to see
some real progress.
왜?
-What?
-I'm 1 2, I'm not stupid.
나 12살이에요
알 건 다 안다구요
- 전화 좀 써도 돼?
- 그럼
Can I use your phone?
혹시 모를까봐 하는 얘긴데
네 손에 든 것도 전화기야
For future reference,
that thing in your hand...
...can also be used as a phone.
되잖아
Yes, it's working.
왜 전화를 안 하지?
-Why isn't she calling?
-Maybe she never got your message.
메시지 못 받았나보지
응답기에 다시 걸어봐
Call her machine,
and if she has a lot of beeps...
삐 소리가 많이 나면
아직 메시지 못 들은 거야
...that means she didn't get
her messages yet.
- 그렇게 하면 내가 너무...
- 궁해 보여? 불쌍해 보여?
-Doesn't that make me seem?
-Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
넌 날 너무 잘 안단 말야
You obviously saw my personal ad.
- 삐 소리 많이 나?
- 직접 받았어
How many beeps?
She answered.
그럴 때는 '여보세요'라고
말하는 거야
This is where you'd use
that "hello" word.
절대 말 안 할 거야
메시지 받고도 전화 안 하는 거야
I won't talk to her.
She got my message...
...and is choosing not to call me.
Now I'm needy and snubbed.
난 궁한데 무시당했어
그냥 궁하기만 하면 좋은데
God, I miss just being needy.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
어떻게 됐어?
So how'd he take it?
솔직히... 잘됐지
Pretty well, actually.
- 레이첼?
- 응?
네 머리카락에 왜 치실이
붙어있니?
How come you have
dental floss in your hair?
그래?
Oh, do l?
병원 의자에서 섹스했어
-We ended up having sex in his chair.
-You had sex in his chair?
병원 의자에서 섹스했어?
내가 너무 크게 말했지?
I said that a little
too loudly, didn't l?
뭘 했다고?
You had what?
의자에서 섹스했대
Sex in his chair.
무슨 생각을 한 거야?
What...? What were you thinking?
모르겠어
우린 아직도 서로를 좋아해
I don't know.
We still care about each other.
단칼에 잘라버릴 수가 없어
There's a history there.
It's like you and Carol.
너랑 캐롤처럼
아니, 아니!
나랑 캐롤 얘긴 하지마
It's nothing like me and Carol.
캐롤이 지금 "로스, 이 소파에
앉아봐" 하면 뭐라고 할 거야?
If she said to you,
"Ross, I want you on this couch...
... right here, right now,"
what would you say?
내가 옆으로 비킬게
If it helps, I could slide over.
우리랑은 상황이 달라
사과와 오렌지 같은 거라구
It's a totally different situation.
It's apples and oranges.
치아교정사와 레즈비언이야
난 갈래
It's orthodontists and lesbians
I gotta go.
어디 가려고?
-Where are you going?
-I just have to go.
그냥 가는 거야
꼭 이유가 있어야 돼?
I have things to do with my life.
나도 할 일이 있다구
할 일이 산더미 같이 쌓였어
I have a jam-packed schedule.
다 하려면 멀었어, 알아?
And I am late for keeping up
with it, okay?
여보세요, 여보세요?
여보세요?
민디!
Mindy.
잘 지내?
How are you?
그럼, 들었어
축하해, 잘됐어
Yes, I heard. Congratulations.
That is so great.
정말? 세상에
Really, oh, God
그래
내일 근무하는데
오고 싶으면 와도 돼
I'm working tomorrow, but if you
want, you can come by if you'd like.
좋아
그래
Great.
좋아
그래
그럼 내일 보자
So I'll see you tomorrow.
그래, 안녕
Okay. Bye.
맙소사, 어떡해
난 몰라
Oh, God. Oh, God.
민디는 잘 있어?
So how's Mindy?
내일 날 만나러 온대
She wants to see me tomorrow. She
sounded weird. I gotta call Barry.
목소리가 너무 이상했어
배리한테 전화해야지
안녕, 나야...
It's me. I just
Mindy.
민디!
민디, 너 거기 있을 줄
알고 걸었지
Mindy. No, I figured
that's where you'd be.
지옥엔 너같은 애들이
우글거릴 거야
Hell is filled
with people like you.
그 사람 또 왔어
He's back.
The peeper's back.
엎드려
-Get down.
-Get down?
- 엎드려?
- 엎드려서 푹 쉬어
And boogie.
고맙지만 일하러 가야 돼
민디한테 얼굴 긁힐 각오해야지
I gotta go and get
my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
걱정하지 마
아직 모를지도 몰라
She may not even know.
7개월 동안 감감무소식이더니
갑자기 전화를 했어
I haven't heard from her in seven
months, what else is it about?
다른 이유가 있겠어?
나랑 제일 친한 친구였는데...
She was my best friend.
캠핑도 같이 가고 나한테
키스하는 것도 가르쳐줬지
We went to camp together,
she taught me how to kiss....
그랬어?
그런데 이젠 아주 남이 됐어
Now, you know,
I'm, like, the other woman.
- 내가 너무...
- 밝혔지
-I feel so
-Naughty.
나중에 보자
-See you later.
-I'll walk with you.
잠깐, 데려다줄게
레이첼, 키스하는 거 배울 때
유니폼 입고 했어, 아님...
When she taught you to kiss, were you
wearing any kind of little uniform?
알았어
That's fine, yeah.
나 화장실 갈 건데
전화기 좀 봐줄래?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Will you watch my phone?
가져가면 되잖아
-Take it with you.
-We haven't had a second date...
첫 번째 데이트밖에 못했는데
쉬 소리 들려주라고?
-...she needs to hear me pee?
-Why don't you call her?
네가 하지 그래?
안돼, 메시지 남겼잖아
나도 자존심이 있어
I can't. I left a message.
I have some pride.
- 정말?
- 아니
-Do you?
-No.
다니엘, 안녕
Danielle, hi.
나 챈들러야
It's Chandler.
잘 있지
I'm fine.
나한테 전화했는지 궁금해서
걸었어, 나도 참 바보지
Listen....
I don't know if you tried
to call me because...
전화기를 꺼놨지 뭐야
... I accidentally shut off my phone.
그래, 알았어
그렇게 해
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
통화 중이라고
다시 전화 걸겠대
She's on the other line.
She's gonna call me back.
통화 중이라고 다시 전화한대
She's on the other line,
she's gonna call me back.
화장실 급한 거 아니었어?
-Don't you have to pee?
-That's why I'm dancing.
그러니까 춤추잖아
민디!
-Mindy.
-Hey, you.
안녕
Hey, you.
어떻게 지내?
So what's up?
우리 좀 앉을까?
We should really be sitting for this.
그러자
Sure we should.
그래...
한 번만 물어볼 테니까
솔직히 대답해 줘
I'm gonna ask once,
and I want a straight answer.
빙빙 돌리거나 쓸데없이
기다리게 하는 거 질색이야
Not like when I asked if those red
pants made my ass look big.
요즘 상황이 좀 이상하게
돌아가는데
I know things have been weird...
넌 나랑 제일 친한 친구야
로리 스케이퍼를 빼면...
...but you're my oldest friend,
except for Laurie...
근데 그 애랑은 절교했어
살 좀 뺐다고 좋아하는데
...who's bitter because
she lost weight...
얼굴은 하나도 안 예뻐졌거든
...and it turns out,
she doesn't have a pretty face.
대답해줄 거지?
-Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
-Okay.
그래
내 들러리가 돼줄래?
Will you be my maid of honor?
당연하지
-Of course.
-That's so great.
잘됐다
It is. It is. It is.
- 물어본다는 게 그것 뿐이야?
- 그것 뿐이야
-That's all you wanted to ask?
-That's all.
왜? 왜 그래?
-What?
-That's not all.
그게 다가 아냐
- 그럴 줄 알았어
- 그것 뿐이 아냐
-Oh, sure it is.
-Oh, no, it isn't.
배리가 누굴 만나는 것 같아
I think Barry's seeing someone
in the city.
왜 그렇게 생각해?
What would make you think that?
약혼 발표한 뒤로
행동이 너무 이상해졌어
Since the engagement,
he's acted weird.
어젯밤에 집에 왔는데
샤넬 향수 냄새가 나는 거야
And then last night, he came home
smelling like Chanel.
정말?
Really?
이렇게 말하면
기분이 나아질지 모르겠지만
If it'll make you feel any better...
나랑 약혼했을 때도
이상한 행동을 했었어
...when Barry and I got engaged,
he was weird too.
내가 두려워하던 게
바로 이거였어
Oh, God.
That's what I was afraid of.
뭘 두려워했는데?
What's what you were afraid of?
좋아, 솔직히...
배리가 너랑 약혼했을 때
When Barry was engaged to you,
he and l...
몰래 날 만나고 있었거든
... kind of had
a little thing on the side.
- 뭐?
- 알아, 그래
-What?
-I know, I know.
그이가 나한테 프로포즈했을 때
네 얘길 하면서 다들 말렸어
When he proposed, people said, "He'll
do to you what he did to Rachel."
내가 너무 바보 같아
And now I feel so stupid.
민디
그래, 넌 바보야
You are so stupid.
우린 둘 다 바보야
We are both so stupid.
무슨 소리야?
What do you mean?
- 낯익은 냄새지?
- 설마
Smell familiar?
정말 미안해
Oh, I'm so sorry.
- 아냐, 내가 미안해
Oh, no, me.
I am so sorry.
No, I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
오, 예!
Oh, my.
두 글자, 동그라미 혹은 원
Four letters, "circle or hoop."
울려라, 울려
-Ring, damn it, ring.
-Thanks.
'원형'
우리 전화 안 되는 거 알아?
-You know our phone's not working?
-What?
뭐?
커피숍에서 전화했는데
아무도 안 받던데
I called and there was no answer.
내가 꺼놨어
I turned it off.
기막혀라, 내가 꺼놨어
Mother of God, I turned it off.
네가 말한 대로네
Just like you told her you did.
내가 틀린 말했어?
Just pointing out the irony.
있잖아, 내가 길 건너편
건물에 가서 알아냈어
I went across the street
to the doorman.
우리 훔쳐보는 사람 말야
I got the peeper's name.
Can I use the phone?
전화 써도 돼?
Can I use your phone?
시드니 막스 전화번호요
The number for a Sidney Marks, please.
난방 장치는?
"Heating device."
라디에이터
Radiator.
네 글자
Five letters.
난방 장치
"Rdtor."
시드니 있어요?
Yeah, is Sidney there?
댁이라구요?
Oh, this is? Sidney's a woman.
여자야
여자면 어때서?
So she's a woman, so what?
맞아, 여자면 어때서
Yeah, so what?
이봐요, 난 건너편에 사는데
망원경으로 쳐다보는 거 알아요
I live across the street, and I know
about your telescope.
상당히 불쾌해요
And I don't appreciate it.
지금도 보고 있다구요
여기요
Yeah, I can see you right now.
Hello?
집에서 속옷만 입고 다니는 걸
쳐다보면 난...
If I wanna walk around in my
underwear, I shouldn't have to feel
고마워요
Thank you.
그 말을 하려는 게 아니고
That's not really the point.
The point is, that
그러니까 요점은...
- 그야 자유지만 가끔은...
- 조이?
Mostly free-weights,
but occasionally
네, 옆집 사는 친구예요
갈색 머리요
Yeah, my neighbor.
Yeah, the brunette.
너 녹색 드레스 입은 날
정말 예뻤대
She said you looked pretty that day
in the green dress.
녹색 드레스? 정말?
The green dress? Really?
잉그리드 버그만인 줄 알았대
She said you looked like
lngrid Bergman.
거짓말!
내 얘긴 안 해?
Did she mention me?
머리에 왜 타월을 감고
다니냐고 묻는데?
She wants to know why you tie
the towel around your head.
버릇이야
It's a leave-in conditioner, okay?
버릇이에요
It's a leave-in conditioner.
안녕
- 안녕
- 시간 있어?
그럼, 그럼
들어... 와
-You got a second?
-Sure, sure.
Come on...
안녕, 자기야
-...in.
-Hello, sweetheart.
두 사람 여긴 웬일이야?
What you guys doing here?
자기랑 헤어지려고 왔지
We are here to break up with you.
누가?
Both of you?
자기는 나쁜 사람이야
자기는 천벌을 받아야 돼
We think you're a horrible person,
and bad things should happen to you.
미안해, 미안해
정말 미안해, 내가 바보였어
I'm sorry.
God, I am so sorry.
I was weak.
I couldn't help myself.
어쩔 수가 없었다구
무슨 짓을 했건 당신을 너무
사랑하기 때문이야
Whatever I did, I only did
because I love you so much.
누구한테 하는 얘기야?
Which one of us
are you talking to there?
민디! 물론 민디지
난 늘 민디를 생각했어
Mindy.
Of course, Mindy.
It was always Mindy.
저 의자에서 섹스를 하고도?
When we were having sex
in that chair?
진심이야, 내가 무슨 짓을 했건
항상 당신만 생각했어
I swear, whatever I was doing,
I was thinking of you.
그만해!
Please. That second time, you couldn't
have picked her out of a lineup.
두 번이나 하면서도
민디 생각은 하지도 않았잖아
두 번이나 했어?
You did it twice?
몇 번이냐가 중요한 게 아냐
배리라는 게 중요하지
The first time didn't really count.
You know, it was Barry.
- 맞아
- 민디, 자기야
Honey, sweetheart, look.
Just give me another chance.
제발 한 번만 기회를 줘
우리 다시 시작하는 거야
We'll start over.
We'll go back to Aruba.
우리, 아루바로 가자
아루바랑 무슨 사연 있어?
What is it with you and Aruba?
Do you have a deal with the airlines?
거기 항공사하고 계약이라도
맺은 거야?
어때?
What do you say?
파베르 박사님, 응급 상황입니다
Dr. Farber, we've got
an emergency here.
제이슨 카스탈라노가
숨이 막힌다고 합니다
Jason Castalano 's choking
on his retainer.
저런, 지금 갈게요
Oh, God.
I'll be right there, Bernice.
제발 가지 마, 알았지?
금방 올게
Look, please don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
좋아, 기다리면서
자기 욕하고 있을게
Okay, and we'll be here,
hating you.
걸어나가면서
땀 삐질거리는 거 봤어?
See how he was sweating
when he walked out?
온몸에 기름 발라서
꼬치에 끼워 불에 구우면
If I'm hogging the ball,
you jump right in there...
기분이 날아갈 텐데!
...and take some punches.
This feels great.
그래도 나 그이랑
결혼하고 싶어
I'm pretty sure
I'm still gonna marry him.
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
민디, 저 인간은 악마야
Mindy, the guy is the devil.
가운 입은 사탄이라구
He is Satan in a smock.
그래, 완벽하지는 않지
I know he's not perfect.
하지만... 그래도...
But the truth is at the end of
the day, I still really wanna be...
난 배리 파베르 박사님
사모님이 되고 싶어
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
사모님이라구
... D. D.S.
못 말려
Oh, God.
너도 행복해지는 방법을
찾으면 좋겠어
I hope you can find a way
to be happy for me.
내 들러리 돼주는 거지?
And I hope you'll still be
my maid of honor.
배리가 아루바에서
너 잡아먹지 않기만 바랄게
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you
and eat you in Aruba.
괜찮아?
You okay?
응
정말?
Really?
그래
배리를 두고 나온 후, 내가
옳은 선택을 했는지 궁금했는데
Since I ran out on Barry
at the wedding...
...I've wondered whether I made
the right choice.
이젠 알았어
And now I know.
다행이야
I'm so glad.
또야?
Big day.
좋아, 이건 어때?
'땅콩'이 더 옷을 잘 입어
I'll give you this:
Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
외알 안경도 쓰고
모자도 쓰고...
He's got the monocle,
he's got the top hat....
호모인 거 알아?
Did you know he's gay?
분명히 짚고 넘어가자
너 '땅콩'이랑 데이트할 거야?
I just wanna clarify this.
Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
챈들러?
다니엘, 안녕?
Danielle, hi.
얘들아, 여긴 다니엘
다니엘, 친구들이야
Everybody, this is Danielle.
Danielle, everybody.
- 안녕
웬일이야?
계속 전화했는데
전화번호가 틀렸더라구
Why are you here?
I've been calling,
but I had your number wrong.
나중에 다시 전화했는데
받질 않는 거야
When I got the right one,
there was no answer.
그래서 괜찮은지 보려고
한번 와봤지
So I thought I'd come down here
and make sure you were okay.
난 괜찮아
우리 다음에 다시 만날까?
I'm okay.
Maybe we could get together later?
그거 좋지, 전화할게
자기가 하든가, 어쨌든...
That sounds good. I'll call you.
Or you call me, whatever.
- 알았어
- 그래
You got it.
- 안녕, 여러분
- 안녕
-Bye, everybody.
-Bye.
- 잘됐다
- 두 번째 데이트네
-There you go.
-Second date.
모르겠어
I don't know.
모르겠다구?
다니엘도 근사하고
다 좋은데
You don't know?
She seems nice, but her coming
all the way here...
내가 괜찮은지 보려고
여기까지 와봤다잖아
...just to see if I was okay?
I mean, how needy is that?
얼마나 궁하면 그래?
세상에